taxi2airport.com 2019-02-03

# Privacy Policy - Taxi2airport.com

**Taxi 2Airport.com** is owned by TAXI2AIRPORT.COM B.V. **Taxi 2Airport.com** stands for responsible data management of our users. Your personal data is carefully being handled and secured. The aim of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about how **Taxi 2Airport.com** is using your personal data, collected on our website, and to explain how to change or delete this data. **Capturing and processing of personal data** **Taxi 2Airport.com** collects and processes your personal data, like your email address, IP-address and name/address/city for the following purposes:

  1. When placing an order, we need your name, email address, home and destination address and payment details to process your order and to keep you informed on the progress of your order.

  2. In order to make your booking experience at **Taxi 2Airport.com** as pleasant as possible, we collect and save, with your permission, your personal details and the details of your order and the usage of our system. This enables us to personalize the website and to recommend services you might like.

  3. To keep you informed on interesting offers of products and services of other TAXI2AIRPORT.COM BV entities and on products and services of carefully selected partners of TAXI2AIRPORT.COM BV.

  4. When creating a TAXI2AIRPORT.COM account we save your details on a Secure Server. In your **Taxi 2Airport.com** account we save information like your name, address, phone number, email, home and destination address and payment details to make future orders more easy.

  5. Details on the usage of our site and feedback we get from our visitors enables us to further develop and improve our website.

**Securing your details** **Taxi 2Airport.com** makes use of of strict safety procedures, to prevent unauthorized people making use of your details. Your personal details are safe with TAXI2AIRPORT.COM. We appreciate your trust in us and therefore will extremely carefull handle your details. We make use of one of the most modern techniques: Secure Socket Layer. Your details will be protected at all time and we will be handled confidentially. **Use and removal of cookies** When offering their electronical services, **Taxi 2Airport.com** makes use of 'cookies'. A cookie is a small file being saved on the hard disk of the computer. Cookies do not harm your computer in any way. Furthermore cookies don't give insights in personal usage so do not contain name or an email address. **Taxi 2Airport.com** only uses cookies to recognize you with a next visit to the site. Cookies enable us to collect data on the usage of our services and to improve and adapt to the requirements of our users. Our cookies provide information with regard to personal identification. If you like, you might set up your browser to prevent TAXI2AIRPORT.COM in collecting cookies. On your own computer, via the browsersettings, you are able to delete already placed cookies and refuse us in collecting new cookies. The procedure how to change these settings depends on your browser, if necessary please consult the ‘Help function’ of your browser. Furthermore you might change most used cookies being placed using the TAXI2AIRPORT.COM website and/or refuse both individually and collective via www.youronlinechoices.com/nl/uw-advertentie-voorkeuren. This also shows which of the cookies are live at your browser. After deleting/erasing cookies, you are still able to see ads. **Updates** **Taxi 2Airport.com** keeps the right to one-sided make changes to this Privacy Policy. Changes or additions on the Privacy Policy will be published in this section. Therefore please check the Privacy Policy on regular basis. If you might have questions on our Privacy Policy, please contact our customer service via our contact form or by phone. Our customer service is here to help you, might you need information on your details or want to change them. You have the right to change your details. TAXI2AIRPORT.COM B.V. te Amsterdam Customer service, Weteringschans 28, 1017SG, Amsterdam Phone +31 88 3188 331. Latest update: 01-02-2016.
